Omisakin Olatunji | Pure and Applied Chemistry Graduate

5, Omisakin Street, Abule Egba, Lagos State | 09068900830 | msknolatunji@gmail.com. Github Link: https://github.com/Tunji545?tab=repositories.

Personal Profile

'An enthusiastic programmer with healthy curiosity for advancement in the tech ecosystem coupled with the ability to blend easily with new tools and languages'

With in-depth knowledge in some basic programming concepts like Object Oriented Programming (OOP) and specializes using JavaScript, I have proven ability working with some JavaScript Frameworks like React, Bootstrap, also CSS Pre-processors like LESS and SASS (Syntactically Awesome Style Sheets) among others.

Core Skills

•	JavaScript.	•	MS-Office: Word, PowerPoint.
•	React.	•	CSS Pre-processors – LESS.
•	Bootstrap.	•	CSS Pre-processors – SASS (Syntactically
•	NodeJS.		Awesome Style Sheets).
•	Task Runners – Grunt and Gulp.		

Hard and Soft Skills

•	Business Etiquette.	•	Employability Skills.
•	Critical Thinking.	•	Innovation
•	Effective Communication.	•	Emotional Intelligence and TeamWork.
•	Personal Effectiveness.	•	Skillful with MS Word, PowerPoint.

Educational Background

Hong Kong University of Science and	Technology (Coursera)	Front-End Web UI Frameworks	and Tools:			
Bootstrap 4			2020			
Hong Kong University of Science and	Technology (Coursera)	Front-End Web Development w	ith React			
2020						
Hong Kong University of Science and Technology (Coursera) Server Side Development with Node						
Express and MongoDB						
John Hopkins University (Coursera)	HTML CSS and JavaScript for Web Development		2020			
FreeCodeCamp	Responsive Web Design		2020			
FreeCodeCamp	eCamp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures		2020			
Jobberman	Jobberman Soft-Skills Training		2020			
OpenClassroom Learn Programming with JavaSo		ith JavaScript	2019			
OpenClassroom	Build Your First Web Pages with HTML and CSS		2019			
OpenClassroom	Think Like a Computer: The Logic of Programming		2019			
Ladoke Akintola University of Techno	logy (LAUTECH) Ch	nemistry Dept. Bachelor of Techno	ology			
(B.Tech with honours)	Th	aird Class	2012 - 2018			
Paragon Group of Schools, Abeokuta	S	SCE	2003 - 2009			
Malomo Nursery and Primary School,	Abule Egba FS	SLC	1998 - 2003			

Work Experience

Pan African Institute for Global Affairs and Strategy (PAIGAS)

PAIGAS Ambassador: 2019 – 2020.

Undertook several sensitization campaigns against irregular migration in my place of primary assignment. Planning and mapping out strategies on ways to convince the indigenes on the danger of illegal routes e.g. Sahara Desert, as a means of leaving one's native country. Engaging in Community Development service once in a month and also carrying out several projects. For example, mounting a gigantic billboard on the main road in Dutse, visible to commuters, warning them against engaging in irregular migration.

Government Day Secondary School, Madobi.

Head of Chemistry Department: 2019 – 2020.

Drafting of lecture notes, assignment and setting of examination questions also the marking of the candidates' solutions to the questions. Preparing the final year students for the promotional external examinations like NECO and WAEC.

National Youth Service Corps (NYSC).

A corps member: 2019 - 2020.

West African Examinations Council (WAEC)

Examiner: 2019.

Marking of the candidates' Chemistry papers answer scripts in the year 2019 with other examiners.

Chemiron International Limited

Casual Worker: 2018

We took the encapsulated product (blood tonic) from the Encapsulating room to the Blistering room. I then took the encapsulated product and blistered them. I check the deformed capsules from the Encapsulating room to separate them from being blistered. I also trimmed the leaflets of the blistered products to the right shape before moving them to another room where they will be neatly packed into cartons of various sizes.

Chemiron International Limited (Industrial Training)

Quality Assurance Personnel: 2015 – 2016.

I performed both qualitative and quantitative tests on the various raw materials used for production of blood tonic capsules as well as on the blistered capsules from the Blistering room to ascertain the accuracy of the various nutritional contents claimed before being sold out for consumption. We also perform various toxicological tests on the blistered products to make sure the products are safe for consumption.

Referees

Based on request.